(Stuart:)- Hey, Leonard.
- Oh, hi.
- How's it going?
- Good, good.
(Leonard:)- You?
- Fine.
- Oh, yeah, hey, can I ask you something?
- Sure.
(Penny:)You know your friend Stuart?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Penny:)Well, he asked me out again
and I said yes.
(Penny:)And then I started thinking
maybe I should talk to you first.
- About what?
- Well, does it bother you?
(Penny:)Me going out with one of your friends?
- Because, you know, you and me...
- No. No, that's the past.
(Leonard:)I'm really more of a right now
kind of guy.
(Leonard:)You know, living in the moment.
(Leonard:)Although I do have to live a little
in the future because, well, that's my job.
(Leonard:)Of course, my fondness for classic science
fiction does draw my attention backwards...
(Leonard:)...but those stories often take place
in the future, so...
(Leonard:)In conclusion, no, it doesn't bother me.
(Penny:)Okay, well, that's really cool of you.
LEONARD:
Yeah? Well, I wouldn't say cool.
I'd just say, "That's Leonard."